I've built websites, I mean online stores before that had so many products and even with automations
it would take hours. This I mean you'll see when we get to, well we'll add a product through ChatGPT
and I mean you could hand this off to someone with literally no technical knowledge.
ChatGPT walks you through everything. You tell it what image goes to the hero, what image goes to
the thumbnail, and it routes it through automatically cropping it, putting it on the
content network server, and then putting the whole page together providing it to you so that you can
preview it and then you publish. And then of course there's coupons and shipping and basically the
rule of thumb when we were building this was that ChatGPT needed to be able to do everything that
you needed to do.
You need to do to manage the website and then we mirrored those same actions in creating the
administrative backend kind of dashboard where you can also go to do things you know if
for whatever reason ChatGPT was down. Cool so with that let's get started.